Kizukanai futari najimino nai hibi ga
Two people who don't realize, the days that are not known to them
Ato kara Oikakete kuru
Will chase after them.
Those who lost a place to run, smile slightly.
'Now it's time,' the clock declares.
Consciousness in my heart,
Before it slips away, I want to see you.
Inside the box where no past and even no tragedy exist,
I want to close the world within.
Confused Memories
I want to hide behind the gentle tears,
Where is the freedom?
It's here.
Found it.
That hanging corpse vanished into the thin air, you say?
Yeah.
Then, lot of students have claimed to witness it.
Finally, the exit was sealed shut.
The forbidden biology room thus become one of the seven mysteries of Fudoh High.
Academy's Seven Mysteries Murder Case
File
The forbidden biology room?
You haven't heard of it before?
It's one of the seven mysteries.
You mean, there are six more?
In that old building.
Yeah.
The second, a severed hand in the printing room.
The third, the bloody fountain.
We know up to the sixth,
but the seventh is still a mystery.
They say, if you know the last one, you'll be murdered.
By the "after-school magician."
The "after-school magician?"
Yeah, we don't know his identity,
But the rumor says he lives in the old building.
No way...
B-blood!
No, it's not. Look.
Ketchup!
I'm full-
Hajime-chan!
I saw you skipped class, and just as I
thought, you're at a place like this!
Miyuki, the omelet was really delicious.
Thank you!
This is my...
I ask for something more filling tomorrow.
My ankle!
I can't believe this.
Kindaichi Hajime, the lowest among the humanity.
I heard he got a zero in math again.
It's hard to believe he's a childhood friend
with Miyuki, one of the best students in school.
Hajime-chan, here.
You already finished my
homework I asked for this morning?
Thank you!
You should do your own homework.
If I always do it for you, it won't help you in the future, Hajime-chan.
You're being cheap!
You were a lot nicer in kindergarten!
"No" means No.
Meanie, please?
No!
Just as usual, Kindaichi-kun.
Sakuragi-senpai...
Leave her alone,
Some octopus-girl that you've been hanging out.
O-octopus!
I'm the only one who understands your hidden value.
Well...
Me?
I'm Sakuragi Ruiko from Mystery Research Club.
Foudou Highschool, Sakuragi Reiko
Third Year
Leave this to me.
Are you going to do it for me, Senpai?
I have a favor to ask you in return.
Kindaichi-kun, I want you solve it,
The Seven Mysteries of Fudoh Academy.
The Seven Mysteries?
This is the first time I've
visited the Mystery Research Club.
Why are you following me, Miyuki?
I don't know what you'd do, Hajime-chan!
I'm just watching over.
Excuse us...
Who are you?
Ah, I'm Kindaichi.
Sakuragi-san told me to come here.
Since that Sakuragi-san scouted you,
I was wondering what kind of person you'd be,
But you don't look anything
close to "deduction smart" to me.
Fudou High
3rd Year
Makabe Makoto
Ah, I thought so!
You're Makabe Makoto-san
who was on the newspaper, right?
The one who won the mystery novel competition.
"The Dead Body Tells Everything"
It's second on the best sellers list.
Makabe-kun is the star in mass media now.
He's nicknamed, "Genius highschooler novelist."
Someone's story didn't pass
even the preliminary, right?
If Matoba-sensei didn't put up my poster there,
Onoue, I could have given you one.
Fudou Highschool, Onoue Takahiro
Third Year
What are you doing...?
Nothing in particular.
Fudou Highschool, Saki Ryuuta
First Year
Go on.
That's creepy.
Sorry.
Thank you.
By any chance, are those the
plastic gloves used for operations?
She has germophobia.
Fudou High
3rd Year Student
Takajima Tomoyo
Somehow I don't think I'll fit in...
We have a problem anyway...
What is troubling you?
No one can read this.
The code that Sakuragi-senpai left.
She said, if you don't know what this means,
You cannot participate in the club camp this time.
It's just some prank that she set up.
H-he's right.
Translator Note: The Golden Week is a collection of four
national holidays within seven days. In combination with well
placed weekends, the Golden Week becomes one of Japan's three busiest holiday seasons, besides New Year's and the Obon week.
The club camp is held on Golden week.
That's great, Hajime-chan!
Using matches as a multiplication symbol is the key, huh?
Easy, easy!
Good job, Kindaichi-kun.
That's stupid.
That's just pure luck.
He's the grandson of the
famous detective, Kindaichi Kousuke.
He's also a genius with an IQ of 180.
He has an IQ of 180?!
Anyhow, let's start the club meeting.
Today's theme is the rumored Seven
Mysteries of Fudoh Academy's old school building.
You mean, the one that if
you find out the seventh secret,
You'll be killed by afterschool conjurer?
That afterschool conjurer,
Sent a threat letter to the Principal.
A threat letter from the afterschool conjurer?
You all know that we're trying to
tear down the old school building, right?
In the threat letter,
It says that if the old school building is demolished,
The seven mysteries will repeat again.
If the old school building is demolished...
The curse...
"Why send such threat?" That is our theme,
And our Mystery Research
Club will solve all the problems,
Of course, we'll uncover the Seventh Mystery as well.
Well, as a guidance teacher
in the Mystery Research Club,
I'd like to say something.
Yes, Matoba-sensei.
Fudou Highschool, Matoba Yuuchirou
Physics Teacher
Along time ago, I heard a student trying
to uncover the seventh secret went missing.
I'm worried something may happen to...
That doesn't sound like words
coming from the physics teacher.
But, the problems...
You mean, you'll be responsible for anything,
Right?
N-no,that's...
Don't worry.
We'll proceed with caution.
This is alright with you, right?
Translator Note: The book title is 'Mystery Research Club
Meeting Minutes.' The Diskette is labeled 'Seven Mysteries Report.'
Here, look.
Mystery Research Club Meeting Minutes,
From 10 years ago...
I found them from the storage.
There might be a key in these to solve this mystery.
You're quite brave, Sakuragi-senpai.
I expect the most out of your capability, Kindaichi-kun.
I'm sure you'll be able to solve this mystery.
I'm counting on you.
Just as I thought, it's right here...
The key to solving the mystery.
It seems solving the mystery is going well.
Makabe-kun, you're still here?
You're cold just as usual.
I only like smart guys.
l am the "Genius highschooler novelist."
Yeah, you are.
If that was really your work,
Then it'd be wonderful.
Dang it, that woman!
Here, as promised.
What if someone sees this?!
If someone finds out, that'd be the end of my fame.
If my deduction is correct,
Then it's...
Oh no, earthquake?
No!
It finally stopped.
This building is really unstable.
W-what is this...
I see...
I got it, the seventh mystery...
Translator Note: The book is titled 'Side dishes 100.'
Hajime-chan,
What do you want for tomorrow's lunchbox?
Sakuragi-senpai,
Why does she get close to me so much?
By any chance, am I sexy?
Hajime-chan, you are...!
Ah, phone call.
This is Kindaichi.
Ah, Sakuragi-senpai.
Yeah, I finally get it.
The last of the seven mysteries.
Really?
Anyhow, come here right now.
I'll show you something interesting.
It was just like my deduction.
But I didn't think it'd be such a scary secret...
He'll be shocked.
The last of the seven mysteries.
I wonder if she's okay.
The rumor says, you'll be killed by
afterschool conjurer if you find that out.
That's just made-up.
It's creepy, the school at night.
You think?
Ah, here...
It was the printing room in old days.
The second of seven mysteries is here.
In old days,
A male student cut his hand off with
the cutting machine in this printing room.
He died due to loss of blood.
Translator Note: Sign reads 'Printing room.'
But after that,
No matter how much everyone
looked, his severed hand went missing.
Ever since, the sound of the
hand creeping around at night...
What, Hajime-chan?
Just now, I heard something weird.
I .
Please stop...
Look, behind you!
Just kidding.
Really! Hajime-chan!
It's dark.
You were called here too?
By that weird phone call?
You really surprised me.
I'm sorry, I was about to turn on the lights,
However, you guys came in just then.
You are all here by Sakuragi-senpai's call?
Mine was a weird male voice.
It said, "There will be a death
ritual at 10 o'clock, so come."
A death ritual?
Hey. what are you guys doing here?!
Sign: Security Officer Room
You were called here by phone?
Yeah.
Security Officer, Tachibana Ryouzou
Officer
Where did Sakuragi-senpai go?
It's 10 o'clock soon.
The time for a death ritual...
Don't say anything scary.
I'm taking a look around.
You guys, go home.
ls it okay to be with you?
Hajime-chan.
I have a weird premonition.
Everyone, wait here.
Well, why don't we patrol around
the old school building instead of here?
I feel like something might happen..
Don't worry, you can see the old
school building from this new building.
Now that I look at it this way, it does look really old.
It'll be torn down soon.
There's light...
That's strange.
That light is coming from the forbidden biology room.
No one should be able to enter.
The forbidden biology room?
That's?!
Sakuragi-senpai?!
W-what?
Senpai!
I'm sure of it.
It's the biology room.
It won't open!
Where's the key?
It's called the "forbidden"
biology room because there's no key.
Damn.
Is something wrong?
Makabe-senpai,
In this room, Sakuragi-senpai was hanged...
By the afterschool conjurer!
The afterschool conjurer?!
What's going on?
Hajime-chan, what's going on?
Saki! You should help us too!
Sorry, I have no free hand.
It disappeared.
The body and the candles...
That can't be!
I saw it with my own eyes!
All the windows are locked.
He didn't exit through the windows.
Then, the thing we saw...
What's wrong, everyone?
Somehow, doesn't this resemble the Seven Mysteries?
The disappearance of a hanged
body from the forbidden biology room...
Don't say stuff like that. It can't be good omen...
Hey, I think I understand what happened last night.
It was just a prank by Sakuragi-senpai.
She said she would show you
something interesting, right?
I hope that's the case...
I wonder if something happened...
Miyuki!
Miyuki, Miyuki!
Trouble!
What?
At the forbidden biology room...
Return to your classrooms quickly.
We're telling you, you cannot come in.
Go back! The classes will start soon.
Hey, stand aside, excuse me.
Hey,you!
This can't be.
Sakuragi-senpai...
Hey, go back to your classroom qui...
Hey...
You...
I expect the most out of
your capabilities, Kindaichi-kun.
I'm sure you'll be able to solve this mystery.
The afterschool conjurer...
ls this your doing?
This case, I'll definitely solve it.
In the name of the famous detective, my grandfather.
You've taught me, such as where flowers bloom,
Also the constellations and the pain love brings.
We talked about many things on that bench.
I found things that I wouldn't have known by myself.
The time passes as fast as how fun things are.
The time between you and I passed like the wind.
I wanted to be with you. closer than anyone else.
What would keep two together.
I thought, would be the two themselves...
Sakuragi-senpai was hanged to death.
The death ritual we witnessed that night is no illusion.
The creepy code she left for me to solve is probably connected to the After school Magician.
The dark shadow creeps upon us from behind and another student is killed yet again.
What? Miyuki is nowhere to be found, you say?!
Miyuki! Where have you gone?!